经典放映室
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
比尔和泰德畅游
比尔和泰德畅游鬼门关
翻译  Boheme-
翻译  Effy17
翻译  冰箱的牛奶
翻译  易碎的绝对
翻译  陈奥奥
翻译  苏葵
校对  苏葵
时间轴  大葱
时间轴  紫夏
时间轴  Caroline
时间轴  树
特别鸣谢  伊森泽生@少年影视派
后期  雷鸣
总监  苏葵
是时候了
It is time.
他们迎来了第二个关键的
They've reached the second crucial turning point
命运转折点
in their destiny.
他们的信息即将被百万人知晓
Their message is about to reach millions.
但是  我们会改变这一切
But... we will change all that.
当我们完成任务之时
When our mission is successful...
世界将不再由这两个蠢货
...no longer will the world be dominated...
留下来的破烂所统治
...by the legacy of these two fooIs!
我们也不再会听到这些
No longer will we hear this:
我们将阻止他们
We will stop them now!
兄弟姐妹们
Brothers and sisters...
准备好了吗
...are we ready?
-我优秀的学生们  你们好  -基站
- Greetings, my excellent pupiIs. - Station.
我们今天继续学习
Today we continue our study
声学混响物理
of the physics of acoustical reverberation.
我来向各位介绍今天最不冒牌的嘉宾
Meet today's most non-bogus guest speakers.
和我们的朋友托马斯·爱迪生打个招呼
Say hello to our friend Thomas Edison.
大家好
Hello there.
为了能在音乐方面对大家有所帮助
To help us on the musical side of things:
这是约翰·塞巴斯蒂安·巴赫
Johann Sebastian Bach.
然后是来自"不再信仰"的詹姆斯·马丁爵士
And Sir James Martin of Faith No More...
他是"不再信仰"精神与神学中心的创始人
...founder of the Faith No More Spiritual and Theological Center.
-基站  -基站
- Station! - Station!
还有来自23世纪的特邀嘉宾
And a special treat from the 23rd century:
莉亚·帕切尔小姐
Miss Ria Paschelle.
你们都知道  帕切尔小姐发明了
Miss Paschelle, as you all know, is the inventor of the...
时空站声音氧化放大电话传送器
...statiophonicoxygeneticamp-lifiagraphiphonideliverberator.
实在很难想象没有它们的世界  对吧
Kind of hard to imagine the world before we have them, isn't it?
大家记住  这周五
Remember, this Friday,
本·富兰克林和艾瑞莎·富兰克林会过来
Ben Franklin and Aretha Franklin will be here.
周六是去巴比伦实地考察  还有强调一点
Saturday is the field trip to Babylonia. And very important:
请务必戴上耳机做作业  再重复一遍
Do not do your homework without wearing headphones. Repeat...
德·诺默勒斯  我曾经的老师
De Nomolos. My old teacher.
鲁弗斯  我的得意门生
Rufus. My favorite pupil.
-我还以为你已经...  -死了
- I thought you were... - Dead?
不
No.
只是在准备
Just in preparation.
我再也受不了这个体制了
I worked within the system until I could stand it no longer.
很快
And soon...
很快  这个体制也将不复存在
...soon the system will never have existed.
-你摆脱不了它的  -时间会证明一切
- You won't get away with it. - Time will tell.
时间已经证明了
Time has told.
那我就回到过去  改写历史
I'll go back and change that,
借助我的秘密武器
with the aid of my secret weapons!
你们好吗  兄弟们
How's it going, dudes?
朋友们  他们都是机器人
Friends, friends, friends. These are automatons.
复制品而已  内置有我的命令
Replicas only. Furnished with my agenda.
你们的任务是什么
Now, what is your mission?
首先  我们将完全消灭比尔和泰德
First, we totally kill Bill and Ted.
对  然后我们接管他们的生活
Yeah. Then we take over their lives.
然后我们彻底毁灭他们
Then we utterly destroy them.
在乐队大战中
At the Battle of the Bands,
我们会做他们要做的演说
we give their speech they are gonna give,
只是完全不一样
except totally different.
我们将开创新的未来  伟大的未来
And thus a new future is born. A great future.
那还用说  老兄  你设计了我们
Don't tell us, dude. You programmed us.
-他就是个机器人  -你也是啊  老弟
- He's totally a robot! - So are you, dude!
我们都是金属脑袋
We're total metal heads!
给我停下
Do shut up.
那么
Now.
-何为能量  -恐惧
- What is the fuel? - Fear!
-何为动力  -纪律
- What is the engine? - Discipline!
-何为目标  -秩序
- What is the ideal? - Order!
如何达到目标
And how do we achieve it?
杀死比尔和泰德
Death to Bill and Ted!
待会见  坏蛋
Catch you later, evil dude.
我是比尔·S·普雷斯顿
I am Bill S. Preston...
先生
...Esquire!
这是泰德·西奥多·洛根
This is Ted "Theodore" Logan!
鼓手和键盘手
On drums and keyboards...
来自中世纪英国的美丽公主
...celebrating their fifth year in the 20th century...
正在庆祝她们来到20世纪的第五年
...the beautiful princesses from medieval England.
乔安娜和伊丽莎白
Joanna and Elizabeth.
我们是
And we are...
怀尔德-史泰林
...Wyld Stallyns.
你们老是说你们是世上最伟大的乐队
You keep telling me you're the greatest band in the world,
但你们糟透了
but you stink.
是啊  我们也不懂为什么
Yeah, we don't understand it either.
你们根本不会唱歌
I mean, you can't sing.
女生们都弹得很好  可你们呢
The girIs can play. But you guys?
女生比男生成熟得更早
GirIs mature faster than guys.
而且  她们从15世纪就开始练习了
Plus, they started in the 15th century.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
-她们来自中世纪英国  -泰德  闭嘴
- They're from medieval England. - Ted, shut up.
中世纪英国  爱荷华州
Medieval England, Iowa.
重点是  乐队大战
Guys, the point is the Battle of the Bands
是这里最重大的赛事
is the biggest event in the area.
一等奖有两万五千美元
We're talking about a $25,000 first prize...
两年的唱片合约
...a two-year record deal
以及被重要商业人士发掘的机会
and chances to be seen by the most important people in the business..
我们甚至在12频道有直播
I mean, we're even got live on Channel 12.
如果你们是我  你们会让自己上台吗
Now, if you were me, would you put you guys on?
没门
No way.
看在你们为脆饼奶酪工作的份上
Since you work for PretzeIs 'N' Cheese,
我就给你们一次机会
I'll give you a shot.
太好了
Excellent!
但排在最后一个  午夜时分
But last. Midnight.
那时可能已经没人了
Probably by that time, everyone will be gone.
没关系的  我们已经习惯了
That's all right. I mean, we're used to that.
我们在泰德弟弟初中舞会时赶走了所有人
Yeah, we fully cleaned out Ted's brother's junior high school dance.
他独奏时  他们把《拉邦巴》声音调到最大
They fully turned on "La Bamba" while he was playing his solo.
墨西哥著名民谣
泰德  闭嘴
Shut up, Ted!
小伙子们  帮帮你们自己吧  稍微准备一下
Guys, do yourseIf a favor. Prepare a little.
打磨你们的表演  想一些点子
Work on your act. Think of something.
别担心  沃尔卓小姐  我们不会让你失望的
Don't worry, Miss Wardrobe. We won't let you down.
老弟  我们必须赢得那场比赛
Dude, we gotta win that concert.
市政礼堂
对  然后我们就能向姑娘们求婚了
Yeah, then we could finally propose to the ladies.
我们在脆饼奶酪挣的钱
No. There is no way we can raise a family
没办法养家糊口
on the money we make from PretzeIs 'N' Cheese.
圣迪马斯市政礼堂
我给米茜打个电话  说我们已经上路了
I'll call Missy, tell her we're on our way.
这应该是个最华丽的生日聚会
Should be a most resplendent birthday party.
-准备好了吗  姑娘们  -当然
- Shall we, ladies? - Great, sure.
怀尔德-史泰林
521岁生日快乐
我听说你俩今晚有别的事要庆祝
I understand you two have something eIse to celebrate tonight.
我们要参加乐队大战了
We got into the Battle of the Bands.
如果我们赢了  我就还清向你借的钱
If we win, I'll totally pay you back your money.
那如果你们没赢呢
What if you don't win?
那样的话  我猜
Well, uh, I guess...
可能再去卖点血
Maybe sell more blood.
不如你考虑卖掉几样乐器吧
Perhaps you should think about selling a couple of instruments.
我们永远都为你留了位置  泰德
Of course, we've always got a spot for you, Ted.
还记得我的老朋友
Remember my old friend,
来自阿拉斯加军校的奥茨上校
Colonel Oats from the Alaskan Military School?
-是要问我近来如何吗  泰德  -是的
- "How's it going", Ted? - Yeah.
非常棒
Splendidly.
记住
Remember...
泰德  对你而言还不算太晚
...it's not too late for you, Ted.
也对你们俩都是
For either of you.
对你们四个而言都不算晚
For all four of you.
有刚做好的软糖呢
Fresh fudge.
你好  小奥
Hi, Oatsie.
亲爱的
Darling.
-你们好啊  -你好  米茜
- Hi, guys. - Hi, Missy.
你好  米茜  我是说妈
Hey, Missy. I mean, Mom.
我简直不敢相信米茜和你爸离婚
I can't believe Missy divorced your dad...
然后嫁给了我爸
...and married mine.
泰德  闭嘴
Shut up, Ted.
-你爸看上去很糟  -我知道
- Your dad looks bad. - I know.
然后呢
What's next?
-可能她会嫁给你  -那你就是你自己的继父
- Maybe she'll marry you. - Yeah, then you'll be your own stepdad.
你们可能注意到我们还没给你们礼物
You probably noticed we haven't given you our gifts yet.
那是因为
That's because...
那是因为我们想说
That's because we wanted to say was...
老弟  失陪
Excuse us, dude.
我自己写的
I wrote this myseIf.
我昨晚写的
I wrote this last night.
"伊丽莎白
"Elizabeth..."
"乔安娜
"Joanna...
我独自走过这黑暗的生命之林
as I wander through this dark and Ionely forest of life...
林中猛兽迭出
...surrounded by various beasts...
有熊  毒蛇  还有松鼠"
...bears, vipers, squirreIs..."
"更别提那藤壶和海藻"
"Not to mention barnacles and algae..."
"僧帽水母  海星  河豚  还有鲶鱼"
"...man-of-wars, starfish, blowfish, catfish..."
错了  鲶鱼是淡水生物
Oh, no, that's freshwater.
重点是  我知道我们向你承诺过更好的生活
The point is, I know we promised you a better life than this.
我想说的是
What I mean to say is,
我意识到  我们将你们从英国带走时
I realize when we took you out of England...
说过未来可期
we said the future held some really good stuff.
虽然未来并没有我们所期待的那样美好
Although stuff hasn't worked out how we thought...
不过我们希望  总有一天能变好
it will, we hope.
后天  如果一切如我们所愿
The day after tomorrow, if things work out...
我想说的是...
What this is about is...
-你们愿意...  -嫁给我们吗
- Will you...? - Marry us?
-西奥多...  -我愿意
- Theodore... - I'd love to.
对准那只猫  老兄  对准那只猫
Aim for the cat, dude, aim for the cat!
我在努力了  邪恶泰德  很努力了
I'm trying, Evil Ted! I'm trying!
就差一点
Aw, just missed!
-不算糟嘛  -的确  我们开始破坏吧
- Not bad. - Yeah, let's make it bad.
老兄  我们到了
We're here, dude.
鲁弗斯和你们在一起吗
Is Rufus with you?
稍等
One second.
哥们  我们好像在时光电路里把他甩掉了
Looks like we lost him in the circuits of time, duder.
好极了  那他就永远消失了
Good. Then he's gone forever.
我们计划的第一步
Our first act of business:
毁了那只可笑又乏味的乐队
Destroy that ridiculous, insipid band!
没问题  老兄
You got it, dude!
开工吧
Get to work.
好了
Now!
好好研究这些书
Study these books well.
我的任务完成之时
When my mission is completed...
这会成为新的历史
this will be the new history.
真是个傻帽
What a shithead.
-拜  -拜
- Bye! - Bye!
开车当心
Drive safe!
-老兄  -干嘛
- Dude. - What?
你说我们结婚后  公主会留在我们身边吗
I wonder if after we're married, princesses will stay over with us?
-当然  -我们的女朋友最洁身自好了
- Yeah. - Our girIfriends are most chaste.
-至少她们没和我们老爸约会  -说得对  老兄
- At least they're not dating our dads. - Good point, dude.
-谁啊  -你好  比尔  我是乔安娜
- Hello? - Hello, Bill. This is Joanna.
乔安娜  你怎么这么快就打来了
Hey Joanna! How'd you call so fast?
这不重要  重要的是
It's not important. This is:
伊丽莎白和我聊过了
Elizabeth and I have spoken and
我们决定要退出怀尔德-史泰林
we've decided we're quitting Wyld Stallyns.
什么
What?
-没错  -为什么
- Yes! - Why?
我们觉得你们是废柴
We think you're losers
再也不想见到你们了
and we don't want to see you again.
不是吧
No way!
我们要独自前往沙漠
We're going to the desert to be alone.
-可是  -结束了  再也不见
- But - It's over. Goodbye.
彻底骗到那俩傻冒了
I totally fooled thoes other usses.
是啊  他们真棒
Yeah, they're completely brilliant.
才怪
Not!
-我们离开这里进入第二阶段吧  -基站
- Let's ditch the booth and start phase two. - Station.
这些宝石价值连城
An incredible fortune in stones.
可我愿意用所有宝石换取一把手持移相器
Yet I'd trade them all for a hand phaser.
或一个美味的俱乐部三明治
Or a good solid club.
也许我们该早点向她们求婚
Maybe we should've proposed to them sooner.
怎么可能  泰德
How could we, Ted?
我们连自己的公寓都快供不起了
We could barely afford our own apartment.
这真是最最可悲的事
This is most non-non-heinous.
-我们该怎么办  -我们得找到她们
- What are we gonna do? - We gotta find them.
和她们谈谈
Talk to them.
怎么找
But how?
会是谁呢
Wonder who that could be?
怎么样啊  比尔和泰德
How's it going, Bill and Ted?
泰德  我们又来了
Ted, it's us again.
-比尔  最近如何  -还不错  比尔  你呢
- How's it going, Bill? - Not bad, Bill. And you?
糟透了
Bad.
我们是来解救你们脱离苦海的
We came to help you guys in your most unfortunate situation.
怎么解救
How?
跟我们走  就知道了
Come with us. We'll show you.
好吧
Ok.
失陪  老兄
Excuse us. Dude.
-我有种不祥的预感  -为什么
- I got a weird feeling here. - Why?
说不上来
I don't know.
我们怎么确定他们真的是我们
How do we know these guys are really us?
泰德  我们已经经历过一次了
Ted, we've been through this before.
要不是之前我们自己的干预
If it wasn't for the previous intervention of our future selves...
我们可能穿越历史吗  可能遇到挚爱吗
would we've even passed history? Or met the babes?
可能经历史上最劲爆的历险吗
Or had a most excellent adventure through time?
好吧
Ok.
泰德  如果你真的是我
Ted, if you're really me,
我接下来会伸出几根手指
how many fingers am I about to hold up?
三根
Three.
你答对了
You're right!
出发吧  老兄  我们开车
Let's go, guys. We'll drive.
-泰德  -干嘛
- Ted. - What?
我有预感  我们即将踏上
I have a feeling we're about to embark upon
一次史无前例的探险之旅
a most unprecedented expedition.
-老兄  -干嘛
- Dude. - What?
我的机器老二性奋了
I got a full-on robot chubby.
之后再说  邪恶泰德
Later, Evil Ted.
之后再说
Later.
我好冷
I'm cold.
老兄  能不能开下后面的暖气
Dudes can we have some heat back here?
闭嘴  比尔
Shut up, Bill.
另一个你可真混蛋
That other you's a real jerk.
是啊
Yeah.
我变成他之前  我是出了名的
I get a rumor to be more considerate towards myseIf
体贴关心自己
when I become him.
他说  闭上你的臭嘴
He said, shut your holes!
老兄  我有种很糟的预感
Dude, I got a very bad feeling.
出去
Out.
所以  乔安娜和伊丽莎白在哪里
So, where are Joanna and Elizabeth?
她们不在这里
They're not here.
我们骗了你们的  真相是
We lied. Here's the truth,
我们现在要杀了你们
we're totally gonna kill you now.
-不是吧  -确实是  泰德
- No way! - Yes way, Ted.
我们的设定就是这样
We're fully programmed to do it.
没错  而且我们也想杀了你们
Yeah, and we want to do it too.
你个混蛋  比尔
You dick, Bill!
-老兄  你居然是金属的  -不可思议吧  你看
- You're metal, dude! - I know. Check it out.
开始吧
Let's go.
假货
Bogus.
泰德
Ted.
我们得做点什么
We gotta do something.
老兄  虽然你们要杀了我们
Dudes, even though you're doing this...
我们  我们...
we, we...
我们爱你们
We love you.
死娘炮
Fags!
回见啊  比尔和泰德
Catch you later, Bill and Ted!
太棒了  完全对准了那个好人比尔
Yes! I totally loogied on that good dead me!
-我们是火力全开的邪恶机器人  -没错
- We're fully, full-on evil robots. - Yeah!
-我们开车走吗  -不了  那车烂透了
- You wanna take the van? - No, it's beat.
有辆保时捷
There's a Porsche.
保时捷911
1978年款
翻译
去偷不属于你的东西
拿下它
Let's bag it.
基站
Station.
比尔
Bill...
发生什么了
what happened?
泰德
Ted...
我们死了  老兄
we're dead, dude.
-不是吧  -确实是
- No way. - Yes way.
你看
Look.
现在怎么办
Now what?
那是谁
Who's that?
你是谁
Who are you?
泰德
Ted...
那是死神  老兄
it's the Grim Reaper, dude.
过得好吗  死神
How's it hanging, Death?
你们随我来
You will come with me.
不行  我们得去找宝贝们
We can't. We gotta get back to the babes.
泰德  我们去不了  我们死了  老兄
Ted, we can't. We're dead, dude.
我们得阻止邪恶二人组  至少得试试
We gotta stop these evil "Usses." We gotta try.
抱歉  老兄  有复活的办法吗
Excuse us, dude, but is there any way back?
你们可以向我发起挑战
You may challenge me to a contest.
可要是你们输了
But if you lose...
就得留在这里
you will remain here in the afterlife...
永生永世
forever.
要是我们赢了呢
What if we win?
从未有人赢过
No one has ever won.
-老兄  我们得甩掉这家伙  -绝对的
- Dude, we gotta ditch this guy. - Definitely.
可是怎么甩
But how?
拉裤裆
Melvin.
对不起  兄弟
Excuse us, dude...
你的鞋带松了
...but your shoes are untied.
不敢相信我们拉了死神的裤裆
I can't believe we just melvined Death.
希望他追不上我们
Let's just hope he doesn't catch up with us.
圣费尔南多  3公里
帕萨迪纳  32公里
圣迪马斯  50公里
不是吧
No way!
这不好笑
This isn't funny.
干得好  乔安娜
Way to go, Joanna!
我不知道你们被什么附身了
I don't understand what's come over you two.
我们曾经是弱鸡  但现在是金属硬汉
You see, we used to be puss-weeds, but now we're metal.
过来放开玩吧
So get over here and put out!
走吧  今晚你们就别想我们演出了
Let's go. You can forget about us playing tonight.
好吧
Fine.
我想只能这样了
Then I guess that's that.
再见
Yeah, see you.
再会  宝贝们
Catch you later, babes!
泰德  我有个主意
Ted, I have an idea.
在今晚的音乐会上说完德·诺默勒斯演讲后
Tonight the concert after we make De Nomolos' speech...
我们就上了她俩
...let's waste them.
基站  同时把这个老鼠洞废了
Station. In the meantime, let's trash this lame rathole.
太棒了  邪恶泰德
Stellar, Evil Ted!
-泰德  我们必须阻止他们  -是啊  但怎么做
- Ted, we have got to stop them. - Yeah. But how?
希望这有用
I hope this works.
在《驱魔人》第一部和第三部里都有用
It worked in The Exorcist. I and III!
赫希菲尔德
All right, Herschfeld.
你调去市中心  狄洛奇就可以休产假
You'll move downtown so DeLoach can take her maternity leave.
我们还要安排一些轮岗
AIso, we need to make a few shifts,
有人想值晚班吗
anyone interested in moonlighting...
我们要加强今晚举办乐队大战的
...we're stepping up security of the amphitheater tonight
露天剧院的安保
for the Battle of the Bands.
我听说你儿子的乐队要表演
I hear your son's band is playing.
多谢提醒  警长
Thank you for reminding me, sergeant.
此外  斯科特·弗兰克
AIso, Scott Frank...
-现在怎么办  -我不知道
- So, how do we do this? - I don't know.
不如你试试
Why don't you try yourseIf?
好吧
Okay.
各位兄弟
Okay, dudes.
我是说  警察同僚们
I mean, fellow policemen...
我儿子  泰德·西奥多·洛根
...my son, Ted "Theodore" Logan...
和他的朋友比尔·普雷斯顿先生
...and his friend Bill Preston, Esquire...
被人谋杀
...have been murdered and
并被来自未来的邪恶机器人代替
replaced by evil robots from the future.
你真的做到了  兄弟
You totally did it, dude!
我附身了我老爸
I totally possessed my dad.
好了
Okay.
你们要去逮捕这些机器人
You got to go over and arrest these robots
这样他们不会毁了我和比尔的一切
so they don't ruin everything for me and Bill.
我的儿子和比尔
I mean, my son and Bill.
最重要的是  他们不会伤害宝贝们
And, most importantly, they don't hurt the babes.
公主们
The princesses.
这没用
This isn't working.
-帮我一把  兄弟  -好的  兄弟
- Back me up, dude. - You got it, dude.
我完全相信你  兄弟
I totally believe you, dude.
-甜甜圈  -太棒了
- Doughnuts! - Excellent!
美味小煎饼
Savory cruller.
-我死了以后超饿  -是啊
- I got really hungry being dead. - Yeah!
比尔  我觉得他们不相信我们
Bill, I don't think they believe us.
我们要找到会相信的人
We have to find someone who will.
再会  警察兄弟们
Catch you later, cop dudes!
泰德  我们不能这样出去
Ted, we can't go like this.
谢谢老爸
Thanks, Dad.
-早上好  -警长
- Good morning. - Sergeant.
甘地
Gandhi.
安·博林
Anne Boleyn.
亚里士多德
Aristotle.
切斯特·艾伦·阿瑟总统
President Chester A. Arthur.
克拉克·盖博
Clark Gable.
查理大帝
Charlemagne.
我想和泰·柯布对话
And I would like to contact Ty Cobb.
-这个降神会有用吗  -没有
- Has this séance stuff ever worked? - No.
但今天会的  兄弟
But it will today, dude.
来自阴间的伟大灵魂啊
Oh, great spirits from the netherworld...
离开你们的安逸居所  向我们传授
...leave your celestial abode and speak upon us...
你的人生经验
...with your life lessons.
我感觉有神灵降临
I feel the spirits have arrived!
近来如何
How's it going...
新时代的兄弟们
...New Age dudes?
神灵  你能听到我吗
Spirits, can you hear me?
能
Yeah.
而且我们可以看到你的...
And we can totally see down your...
那是你妈妈  泰德
It's your mom, dude!
你说得对  让开一点  兄弟
You're right! Move over, dude.
神灵  你要对我们说什么
Spirits, what have you to say to us?
公主们有麻烦了
Okay. The princesses are in trouble.
泰德和他最好的朋友比尔
Ted and his most excellent friend Bill...
被人谋杀了
...were killed!
-听我们说  -你滚开
- Listen to us. - You must go.
小心邪恶鬼魂
Beware of the devil ghosts!
《摆脱恶灵》
你要警告公主们
You warn the princesses!
来自地狱的恶灵
Oh, evil spirits from Hell...
我送你们回归黑暗的来处
...I send you back into the darkness from where you came!
-她在干什么  -不知道  但感觉不是好事
- What's she doing? - I don't know, but I don't think it's good.
不要啊
No way!
兄弟  这是个无底洞
Dude, this is a totally deep hole.
-现在怎么办  -不知道
- Now what? - I don't know.
-你想玩"二十个问题"吗  -好  我想到一个
- You wanna play 20 Questions? - Okay. I got one.
你是一种矿物吗
Are you a mineral?
是的
Yeah.
你是坦克吗
Are you a tank?
猜对了
Yeah.
不错
Good one!
-还不坏  -能再来一次吗
- Not bad! - Can we do it again?
我已经尽力了
I'm working as hard as I can!
不是吧
No way!
这地方完全不是我想的那样
This is not what I expected this place to look like at all.
我们完全被我们的专辑封面骗了  兄弟
We got totally lied to by our album covers, man.
那是谁
Who's that?
泰德  你以为那是谁  兄弟
Ted, who do you think it is, dude?
我们怎样吸引他的注意
How do we get his attention?
魔鬼的标志  兄弟
Sign of the devil, dude!
-魔鬼老兄  -往下看
- Hey, Devil dude! - Down here!
往下看  兄弟
Down here, dude!
两个小家伙
Two little guys!
大块头  看下面
Big dude! Down here!
兄弟  我有点喜欢这里
Dude, I kind of like this.
太厉害了
Excellent!
我们离开这里吧  兄弟
Let's get out of here, dude.
好
Okay.
泰德  如果我死了
Ted, if I die,
我的麦格戴斯乐队专辑都归你
you can have my Megadeth collection.
但兄弟  我们已经死了
But, dude, we're already dead!
-那就归你了  兄弟  -谢了兄弟
- Well, then they're yours, dude. - Whoa! Thanks, dude.
近来如何  恶魔
How's it going, Beelzebub?
我们可以走吗
So, um... Okay. Can we go now?
你们可以走了
You may go.
谢谢  兄弟
Thanks, dude!
你名声不太好  但你是个不错的兄弟
You know, you got a bad rap, but you're actually an okay dude!
-我们在哪  -不知道
- Where are we? - I don't know.
或许我们该闯闯这些隧道
Maybe we should try one of these tunneIs.
-兄弟  我们在哪  -不知道
- Dude, where are we? - I don't know.
或许我们该试试这些门
Maybe we should try one of these doors.
你先请  兄弟
After you, dude.
现在我们在哪
Now where are we?
那是谁
Who's that?
是奥茨上校
It's Colonel Oats!
不会吧
No way!
先生们
Gentlemen!
欢迎来到地狱
Welcome to Hell.
-不可能  -什么
- No way. - What?!
不可能  长官
No way, sir?
你们俩
You two...
从现在开始
...will do whatever I tell you to do...
按我的命令行事
...from now on.
明白了吗
Is that clear?
-是的  长官  兄弟  -什么
- Yes, sir, dude! - What?!
-是的  兄弟  长官  -什么
- Yes, dude, sir! - What?!
是的  长官  长官兄弟
Yes, sir, sir dude!
趴下  给我做...
Get down and give me...
无限次俯卧撑
...infinity.
愚蠢  可怜  懦弱的白痴
Stupid, pathetic, craven little cretins.
我绝不可能
There is no way I can possibly
-做无限多个俯卧撑  -可怜的蠢货
- do infinity pushups! - Pitiful little morons.
-也许他让我们做女式的  -小丑
- Maybe he let's do girlie style. - Jokers!
你们这些渺小  卑鄙
You petty, base,
恃强凌弱  莽撞的混小子
bully, bullock, bugger billies.
你们根本不强壮  反而弱不禁风
You're not strong! You're silky boys!
像蚕屁股里拉出的丝一样弱
Silk comes from the butts of Chinese worms.
我们得离开这里
We gotta get out of here.
你们就像是虫子或烤小黄油蛋糕
Worm, toasty little butter cakes you are.
给我回来
Get back here!
-兄弟  -怎么了
- Dude. - What?
我想我们都在自己的地狱里
I think we're in our own personal hell.
-我们分头走吧  -好
- Let's split up. - Yeah.
-那样我们能好些  -行
- That way can't get us so bad. - Yeah.
怎么回事
What happened?
真的假的
Bogus!
S·普雷斯顿奶奶
Granny S. Preston, Esquire.
不会吧
No way.
赠迪肯
西奥多
Theodore!
你把弟弟弄哭了
You made your brother cry.
不如
How about...
亲一下
a kiss...
你亲爱的老奶奶  比尔
for your dear old granny, Bill?
我亲爱的
My dear...
过来
Come along.
你偷走了迪肯的复活节篮子
You stole Deacon's Easter basket.
不会吧  这都是十年前的事了
No way. This was 10 years ago!
快过来
Come here now!
那根本一点  一点一点都不吓人
That was non, non, non... Non-heinous!
选择
Choose...
你们的
your...
永恒死法
eternity.
选你自己的吧  死娘炮
Choose your own, you fag!
你这个丑陋  红色的万恶之源
You ugly, red source of all evil!
你们好  姑娘们
Hello, girIs.
-兄弟  -什么
- Dude. - What?
-地狱差劲透了  -绝对的
- Hell sucks! - Definitely!
-你们这些低级生物  -迪肯的复活节篮子
- You all no-nosed salamanders! - Deac's Easter basket!
到奥茨这里来
Come on to Oatsie!
我想要在嘴上亲一下
I wanted one right on the lips!
泰德  这里只有一条路可以出去
Ted, there's only one way out of here, man!
好吧  兄弟  我们必须跟死神对战
Right, dude. We gotta play the Reaper!
选个游戏
Choose your game.
但假如你们输了
But if you lose...
你们将永远
you will stay here in Hell...
留在地狱
forever.
D1
D-1.
军舰棋  横向用字母标记  纵向用数字标记
没打中
Miss.
B3
B... 3.
没打中
Miss.
C6
C-6.
打中了
Hit.
-兄弟  -我知道
- Dude... - I know.
J7
J-7.
J-7...
打中了
Hit.
打中了  你击沉了我的军舰
A hit. You have sunk my battleship.
太棒了
Excellent!
-我就知道他会放在J行  -真聪明  泰德
- I total knew he put it in the J's, dude. - Good thinking, Ted.
你们必须再跟我玩
You must play me again.
-什么  -三局两胜
- What?! - Best two out of three.
不可能
No way!
可以的
Yes way.
《妙探寻凶》
-他在干什么  -我不知道
- What's he doing? - I don't know.
我觉得
I believe...
芥末上校在书房用烛台杀了人
Col. Mustard did it in the study with the candlestick.
对不起  死神  你输了  是李子教授干的
Sorry, Death. You lose. It was Professor Plum.
我刚说的是"李"
I said "Plum."
别扯了  你说的是"芥末"
No way. You said "Mustard!"
我们现在能回去了吗
Can we go back now?
五局三胜
Best three out of five.
我不相信这个家伙
I don't believe this guy.
-七局四胜吗  -没错
- Best of seven? - Damn right!
扭扭乐
右手  绿色
Right hand, green.
左手  红色
Left hand, red.
右脚  绿色
Right foot, green.
右脚
Right foot...
这香港脚
Dude!
怎么样
Well?
我会
I will...
带你们回去
take you back.
你玩得挺好的  死神
You played very well, Death.
尤其是你还穿着厚重的死亡长袍
Especially with your totallly heavy death robes.
别一副高高在上的样子
Don't patronize me.
随便吧  兄弟  关于体育精神你还有好多要学
Whatever dude. You got a lot to learn about sportsmanship.
这边走
This way.
现在我们能回去救宝贝们了
Now we can go back and save the babes.
对  但是比尔  我们回去后
Yeah. But, Bill, when we get back,
要怎么打败我们的分身
how we gonna fight those other usses?
他们比我们强壮  也比我们聪明
I mean, they're totally stronger than us. And way smarter than us.
-是啊  而且他们已经杀过我们一次  -对
- Yeah. Plus, they already killed us once. - Yeah.
稍等一会  老兄
One minute, duder!
好吧  如果我们是正义的人类
OK! If we were good human usses,
我们要打败两个邪恶的机器人分身
we had to fight two evil robot usses...
我们该怎么做
what would we do?
制造正义的机器人分身吗
Make good robot usses?
泰德  好主意  老兄
Ted. Good thinking, dude!
对不起
Excuse us.
-能麻烦你件事吗  死神  -又有什么事
- Excuse me, Death? - Oh, now what?
你能带我们去找可以帮我们的人吗
Could you take us to someone who could help us?
你们打败了我  我听君差遣
You have beaten me. I am at your command.
太好了
Cool!
这边走
This way.
-泰德  -什么
- Ted. - What?
死神并不可怕
Don't fear the Reaper.
我听到了
I heard that.
这太奇怪了
This is most atypical.
欢迎来到天堂
Welcome to Heaven.
我肯定会喜欢这里的
I'm sure I'll enjoy it.
谢谢
Thank you.
-从那里过  -谢谢
- Through there. - Thank you.
欢迎来到天堂
Welcome to Heaven.
-你好  -你们好
- Hello. - Hello.
-谢谢  -不用谢
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
"惟有最平静  最开明的灵魂方能获准进入"
"Only the most serene and enlightened souIs shall gain audience."
兄弟  我们有大麻烦了
Dude, we're in big trouble.
我有个主意  老兄
I think I have an idea, dude.
-你好  -欢迎来到天堂
- Hello. - Welcome to heaven.
聪明人
Wise dudes.
-我们能问你们一个问题吗  -行
- Can we ask you a question? - Okey.
请走这边
Right this way, please.
兄弟  我们在天堂  刚打劫了三个人
Dude, we're in Heaven, and we just mugged three people.
我知道  我们最好在影响到所有人前离开这里
I know. We better get out of here before we ruin it for everybody.
快来  死神
Come on, Death.
你看起来真帅
You look great, dude.
真的吗
You think so?
是的  你很帅
Yeah. You do.
闭嘴
You shut up.
-快来  兄弟  -这并不好笑
- Come on, dude. - It's not funny.
真不敢相信我居然会干这么蠢的事
Can't believe I'm doing this stupid.
我怎么会落到这种可笑的境地
How did I end up in this ridicular situation?
最近怎么样
How's it going?
生命的意义是什么
What is the meaning of life?
每支玫瑰都有刺
Every rose has its thorn
美国毒药乐队发行的《每朵玫瑰都有刺》的歌词
就像每晚过后都见黎明
Just like every night has its dawn
就像每个牛仔
Just like every cowboy
都会唱那首悲伤的歌
Sings a sad, sad song
每支玫瑰都有刺
Every rose has a thorn
我是不是认识你
Don't I know you?
不认识
No.
上帝  你好像还不知道
So, God, as if you didn't know...
我们不是你认为的
we're not the three wise people
耶稣诞生时  东方三个博士受神差遣
追寻星星去寻找耶稣  并向他献礼
那三位智者
that you might have thought we were.
我们不是  我们打劫了三个人
No. We mugged three people
抢了他们的衣服  对不起
and took their clothes. Sorry.
我是比尔·S·普雷斯顿
I'm Bill S. Preston.
我是泰德·西奥多·洛根
I'm Ted "Theodore" Logan.
我们是怀尔德-史泰林
Together, we are Wyld Stallyns!
这位可爱的女士是死神
This lovely lady is the Grim Reaper.
我们比赛赢了他  所以他带我们来这里
He brought us here when we challenged him and won.
那么  好吧
Now, okey.
首先  恭喜你造出了地球
First of all, congratulations on Earth!
它是宇宙中最棒的星球
It's a most excellent planet.
我和比尔享受地球上每一天的生活
Bill and I enjoy it on a daily basis.
更不用说其他伟大的星球了
Not to mention your other great planets.
火星  木星  天王星
Mars, Jupiter, Uranus.
但问题是我们死了
But the point is, we died.
死得相当冤
Most unfairly.
但我们赢得了复生的机会
But we won the chance to come back.
我们要想办法救心爱的女人
We need to construct something to help saving the women we love.
我们没剩多少时间了  所以我们想
And we don't get a lot of time. So we were wondering...
你能帮我们找找人
...could you maybe help us find somebody
会帮我们做点东西的人
who can maybe help us bulild something?
基站
Station.
我们想的是
We were thinking along the lines of ...
找一个科学家之类的人
...maybe a scientist or something.
酷
Cool.
谢了  上帝
Thanks, God.
没错  你是一个正直高尚的造物主
Yeah. You're a just and noble creator.
-我们现在要走了  -你接着好好干
- Okay. We'll be going now. - Keep up the good work.
回见  上帝
Catch you later, God.
抱歉  我被他们拽裤裆了
Sorry. They melvined me.
好了  翻转吧  蛋糕
All right, upside-down cake!
-邪恶泰德  -怎么了
- Evil Ted. - What?
我们没有盘子了
We're out of dishes.
看我的
Check this out.
不错啊  邪恶泰德
Not bad, E.T.
我试试
Let me try.
你肯定是没看到风扇
You totally didn't see the fan.
让我的身体过来把我安上
Tell my body to get over here and get me!
没事  我会把你安上的
That's all right. I'll get you.
我拿到你的头了  兄弟
Got your head, dude.
我一定能抢过你的  兄弟
I'm totally gonna tackle you, dude.
邪恶泰德触地得分
Touchdown for Evil Ted!
我们完全是重金属乐狂人
We're total headbangers.
来吧  上来吧
Come on. There you go.
别浪费时间了  现在就实施计划
Stop wasting time. Proceed with the plan now.
好吧  兄弟
Okay, dude.
你觉得我们挑拨他们的关系怎么样
What do you say we trash their relationships?
我恨他们
I hate them.
我恨机器人版的他们
I hate the robot versions of them.
是你创造了我们  兄弟
You made us, dude.
看来就是这里了  兄弟
Looks like this is the place, dude.
现在我们只需找到那个科学家
Now all we gotta do is find that scientist.
-基站算是个什么名字  -我不知道
- What kind of name is Station? - I don't know.
肯定是个来自未来的家伙
Must be some kind of future guy.
好吧  有几个音节
Okay, how many syllables?
是一出戏  还是一首歌  还是
Is it a play or a song or...?
是一个大物件
It's something big.
我押爱因斯坦赢
My money's on Einstein.
那就是基站吗
That's Station?
你觉得全宇宙最聪明的科学家
Did you assume the most brilliant scientist...
自于地球吗
...in the entire universe would be from Earth?
是啊
Yeah.
是电影吗
Movies?
-九个字  -很好  富兰克林先生
- Nine words. - Good, Mr. Franklin.
火  香烟
Fire? Cigarettes?
-云  是云  -抽烟
- Clouds, clouds. - Smoke?
《虎豹小霸王前集》
Butch and Sundance: The Early Years.
美国80年代西部电影
-死神  -抱歉
- Death! - Sorry.
《警察与卡车强盗3》
Smokey and the Bandit III.
美国80年代动作喜剧
警察就是强盗
Smokey is the bandit!
打扰一下  火星人
Excuse us. Martians?
首先  我的朋友比尔和我要祝贺你们
First, my friend, Bill and I would like to congratulate you...
-玩了一局相当精彩的猜字游戏  -没错
- ...on a most well-played round of charades. - Totally
其次
Secondly,
有人向我们推荐
you've been referred to us...
你们是全宇宙最聪明的科学家
...as the most brilliant scientists in the universe.
你们愿意和我们回到地球
So how would you like to come to earth
帮我们制作正义机器人分身吗
and help us build good robot usses...
然后从邪恶分身那救回两位美丽的公主
...to save two beautiful princesses from bad robot usses?
好极了  基站
Sounds good, Station.
走吧
Let's go.
摇滚吧  死神
Let's rock, Death.
泰德
Ted.
-我们活过来了  -是啊
- We're alive. - Yeah.
但我感觉头被秃鹰啄了
But I think a buzzard was pecking at my head.
你的晚餐结束了  蠕虫兄弟
Dinner's over, worm-dude.
你们还好吧
You guys okay?
死神在哪里
Where's Death?
你没事吧  兄弟
You okay, dude?
我没事
I'm fine.
第一件事  我们要回到镇子收拾一下
First thing on the agenda, we go back to town and we clean up.
然后  我们找到公主们  提醒她们
Second, we find the princesses and warn them.
最后  我们去买制作正义机器人分身需要的材料
Third, we purchase stuff to build good robot usses.
好  我们走
Okay. Let's go.
怎么了  怎么了
What? What?
过来呀  小猫  来这儿  小猫
Here, kitty, kitty! Here, kitty, kitty!
那有一只  兄弟
There's one, dude!
差一点就压到了  兄弟
Just missed, dude.
兄弟  我们到了
Dude, we're there.
好的  我有个主意
Okay. I got an idea.
最近怎么样  女性人类
How's it going, lady humans?
建筑商场
硬件  木材  花园
油漆  管道  电力
好了  基站们  到建筑商场了
Okay, Stations, this is Builders Emporium...
这里是电子产品和机器人原料的仓库
...a repository for electronics and robot materiaIs.
把制作金属分身需要的东西买齐
Get what you need to make metal usses.
-特别之夜准备好了吗  宝贝们  -不  我们不去
- Ready for the big night, babies? - No! We're not going.
我觉得你们必须立马停下来
I think you guys should stop right there.
回见  未来老婆
Catch you later, future wife.
邪恶之气
Evil breath!
你们是谁
Who are you two?
看好了
Well, you see...
我的天啊
Oh my god!
快接啊
Come on.
-有人接吗  -不  她们不在我们家或自己家
- Any luck? - No, they're not at our place or theirs.
我打给你爸试试  可能她们去找米茜了
I'll try your dad's place. Maybe they went to talk to Missy.
你好  洛根住宅
Hello, Logan residence.
我是邪恶比尔·S·普雷斯顿先生  请讲
Evil Bill S. Preston, Esquire, speaking.
是他们  他们死而复生了
It's them! They're back from the dead.
看来我们可以再杀他们一次了
I guess we get to kill them again.
太棒了
Excellent!
草坪精灵阀
升级版吸尘器
玻璃纤维管丝
你很快就会来见我了
See you real soon.
-但这次  我们准备好打败你们了  -对
- But this time we're ready for you! - Yeah!
我想我们也准备好打败他们了
I think we can be ready for them too.
祝你们顺利进入乐队挑战  废柴们
Good luck getting in the concert, losers!
-现在启动终极计划  -没问题  伟大的主人
- Initiate the final plan now. - You got it, great one.
别让我失望
Do not fail me.
金属小丑们
Metallic buffoons.
-"另一个我"是个混蛋  -没错
- That other me is a dick. - Yeah.
我希望两个基站知道他们在做什么
I hope the Stations know what they're doing.
基站  你们在做什么
Station! What are you doing?
兄弟们  现在不是玩游戏的时候
Dudes! This is no time to be playing games!
基站
Station.
摇臂灯
那个是我吧
That one's me, right?
基站
Station.
还不错
Not bad.
你还好吗  正义机器人比尔
How's it going, Good Robot Bill?
你还好吗
How's it doing?
凯特·艾克斯罗德  在KJM12台
Kate Axelrod for KJM channel 12...
在圣迪马斯市大礼堂现场报道
... reporting live from the San Dimas Civic Auditorium.
我们就在第四届乐队大战的火热现场
We're rocking at the 4th annual of the Battle of the Bands.
千万不要换台  我们会宣布
So stay tuned and hold tight until we find out...
谁将成为大赛冠军
... who will be your winner.
第四届圣迪马斯
乐队大战
准备好了吗  该你们上场了
You guys ready? You're up.
女生们去哪儿了
Where are the girIs?
在屋顶斜木上吊着呢  我们会在决赛时杀了她们
They're hanging from the rafters. We're gonna kill them at the finale.
祝你们好运  绅士们
Good luck, gentlemen.
看这个
Check it out.
不错啊
Not bad.
掌声送给煤油炉乐队
Let's hear it for Primus!
圣迪马斯市欢迎乐队大战
基站  他们准备好了吗
Station, are they ready?
基站
Station.
做得不错  兄弟
Excellent work, dude.
-那我呢  我做了假发  -好的  死神
- What about me? I made the wigs. - Okay, Death.
我帮你们买东西  是我推的购物车
I helped do the shopping. I was pushing the cart.
-他们会按我们要求工作吗  -基站
- These work like we asked? - Station.
你是最出色的科学家  基站
You're a most excellent scientist, Station.
别说  你的火星屁股还真是大
Plus, you got an excellently huge Martian butt.
基站
Station.
你可以尽情再次分成两半  并放松一下
Feel free to split in two parts again and relax.
别忽略我的健美臀部  我经常健身呢
Don't overlook my butt. I work out all the time.
收割灵魂也很减脂
And reaping burns a lot of calories.
准备还对抗邪恶分身并拯救宝贝了吗
Ready to take on those evil usses and save the babes?
打败邪恶分身  拯救宝贝
Fight evil usses. Save the babes.
-准备好了吗  比尔  -准备好了  泰德
- Ready, Bill? - Ready, Ted.
来吧  干掉他们
Let's go get 'em.
现在有请今晚的最后一支乐队
And now, the last band of the evening.
怀尔德-史泰林
Wyld Stallyns!
怎么样了  蠕虫们
How's it going, worms?
我是比尔·S·普雷斯顿先生
I'm Bill S. Preston, Esquire!
我是泰德·"西奥多"·洛根
And I'm Ted "Theodore" Logan!
我们一起组成了怀尔德-史泰林
Together, we are Wyld Stallyns!
等等
Hold it right there!
我们才是怀尔德-史泰林
We're Wyld Stallyns!
不  哥们  我们是怀尔德-史泰林
No, dudes. We're Wyld Stallyns!
你们杀了我们  邪恶的金属混蛋
You totally killed us, you evil metal dickweeds!
没错  而且我们会再杀一次
Yeah, and we're gonna do it again!
而且  我们还会杀了你们的女友
Plus, we're gonna totally kill your girIfriends.
别担心  宝贝  我们会救你们
Don't worry, babes! We'll save you.
各位  欢迎基站的创造物
Everybody, say hello to Station's creation!
正义机器人比尔和泰德
Good Robot Bill and Ted!
哥们  我们遇见对手了
Dude, we may have met our match.
向你致敬  好人分身
Kudos to you, good human usses.
-回见了  比尔和泰德  -回见了  比尔和泰德
- Catch you later, Bill and Ted! - Catch you later, Bill and Ted!
-伊丽莎白  -西奥多
- Elizabeth! - Theodore!
-乔安娜  -威廉
- Joanna! - William!
那是谁
Who is that?
你是说
Who are you?
我是谁
Who am I?
我是德·诺默勒斯
I am De Nomolos.
我是他们的主人
I am their master.
我必须确保你们死
And I must see to it that you die.
但首先
But first...
我们现在通过世界各地的所有频道现场直播
We are now transmitting on every channel throughout the world.
我的话
My word!
我想让整个宇宙都见证这一刻
I want the whole universe to behold this...
权力的更迭
... transfer of power.
我们未来的社会
No longer will our future society...
不会再建立于这两个白痴的
... be based on the ideas and the music...
想法和音乐了
... of these two fooIs!
而是会建立于我的想法
They will be based on my ideas...
只有我的想法
...and my ideas alone!
哥们  这情况怎么办  我们没时间了
Dude, how do we get out of this? We don't got any time.
有的  哥们  听着  等我们从他身边逃走后
Yeah, we do, dude. Look, after we get away from this guy...
我们就用电话亭  时间旅行到比赛前
...we use the booth, we time-travel back to before the concert
然后布置一些能抓住他的陷进
and set up the things we need to get him now.
好啊  比如什么
Yeah, like what?
比如沙袋
Like a sandbag.
妙啊
Excellent!
然后再来个笼子
Then we'll get a cage.
我的朋友们
My friends.
我也可以玩时间旅行的游戏
I too can play the time game.
如果你这么做  等我击败你们后
If you do that, once I have vanquished you...
我就回去准备这把钥匙
...I'll go back and set up this key.
还有另一把枪
And another gun.
怀尔德-史泰林最酷炫
没错  老哥  只是你没想到一件事
Right, dude. Only there's one thing you didn't think of.
对  只有赢家能回到过去准备这些
Yeah, only the winners' gonna go back and set things up.
没错  那将会是我们  老哥
Yeah, and that's gonna be us, dude.
我们准备了钥匙  还准备了枪
We set up the key, and we set up the gun.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你的鞋带散开了
Your shoelaces are untied.
拉到裤裆了
Melvined.
你被捕了  伙计
You're under arrest, pal.
干得漂亮  爸
Way to go, Dad!
逮捕他  丹诺
Book him, Danno.
好样的  死神
Good job, Death.
那是谁
Who was that guy?
也许我能回答这个问题  先生们
Perhaps I can answer that question, gentlemen.
沃尔卓小姐  谢谢帮忙
Ms. Wardroe, thanks for the help.
我们绝对...
You know, we definitely...
来吧宝贝  脱掉脱掉
Yeah, take it off, baby!
鲁弗斯
Rufus!
你来这多久了  兄弟
How long you been here, dude?
刚好赶上你们的试镜
Just in time for your audition.
所以你一直是沃尔卓小姐
So you were Ms. Wardroe all along.
还有别人能让你们参加这个比赛吗
Hey, would anyone eIse have let you in this contest?
-不  -朋友们
- No! - Now amigos,
那是查克·德·诺默勒斯  我以前的体育老师
That was Chuck De Nomolos, my old gym teacher.
对了  他是27世纪的仰卧起坐冠军
And, by the way, sit-up champion of the 27th century.
先生  我想该你们登台表演了
And now, gentlemen, I believe the stage belongs to you.
谢了  鲁弗斯
Thanks, Rufus.
哥们  我们还是不会弹
Dude, we stilI don't know how to play.
也许我们该变得强点  泰德
Maybe we ought to get good, Ted.
怎么做
How?
真是个高强度的16个月吉他快速入门课啊  哥们
That was a fast 16 months of intensive guitar training, dude.
是啊  除了两周中世纪蜜月
Yeah, except for the two-week medieval honeymoon.
大家好  圣迪马斯
Hello, San Dimas!
我给大家介绍个小朋友
Let me introduce you to a little friend.
这是小泰德
This is little Ted.
你好  小泰德
Hello, little Ted!
这是小比尔
This is little Bill.
你好  小比尔
Hello, little Bill!
还有我们乐队的其他成员  泰德
Now for the rest of our band, Ted.
康茄舞和邦戈鼓高手  证明了
On conga and bongos, proof that
不能以貌取人
you can't tell a book by its cover...
一个能用一个词表达一切的哥们
...the dude who can make one word mean anything...
基站
...Station!
我们的伴舞
Our backup dancers...
基站最大胆的发明创造
...Station's most bodacious creations...
正义机器人分身
...the Good Robot Usses!
这边
And over here...
是我们的贝斯手  恐怖伯爵
...our bass player, the Duke of Spooks...
吓人博士  一点不黑的男人
...the Doc of Shocks, the Man With No Tan...
请向死亡本尊问好
...please say hello to Death himseIf...
死神
...the Grim Reaper!
无论你是国王或清洁工
You might be a king or a little street sweeper
总有一天你要与死共舞
But sooner or later you dance with the Reaper
释放自己的邪恶天性吧
Get down with your bad seIf!
我真喜欢演艺界
I love show business.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen...
我们造访了过去
...we've been to the past.
我们瞥见了未来
We've been to the future.
我们甚至探索了来生
We've been all around the afterlife.
但你知道吗
And you know...
最好的地方
The best place to be...
就是这里
...is here.
最精彩的时刻
And the best time to be...
就是现在
...is now.
我们只想说
And all we can say is...
燥起来吧
...let's rock!
一  二
One! Two!
一二三四
One, two, three, four!
很好  很好
Right good! Right good!
《圣迪马斯报》
世界见证了怀尔德-史泰林获胜
《旧金山编年报》
怀尔德-史泰林中西部巡演
音乐排行榜
怀尔德-史泰林新专辑排名第一
《伦敦日报》
怀尔德-史泰林在温布尔登体育场演出
《奥斯卡邮报》
怀尔德-史泰林在亚利桑那州大峡谷演出
《华盛顿日报》
比尔和泰德中东巡演  和平成就达成
《科学发现》
怀尔德-史泰林用核武器使用功放
《全球》
空气吉他能消除雾霾
《公路杂志》
死神在印第安那波利斯式赛车中获胜
《体育明星》
比尔和泰德  十年间最佳体育人
《马戏团》
死神录制个人专辑
死神夏日装扮引领新潮流
《每日公报》
查克·德·诺默勒斯与米茜完婚
比尔和泰德走向分裂了吗
《每日新闻》
传言怀尔德-史泰林分裂
道琼斯指数下跌600点
《芝加哥公报》
怀尔德-史泰林分裂为假消息
道琼斯指数报新高
《首秀报》
比尔和泰德改编电影
比尔和泰德
我们对他们毫无怨言
《观察者报》
死神陷入假唱丑闻
《滚石》
死神个人专辑销量走低
加入怀尔德-史泰林
《哈罗德先锋报》
怀尔德-史泰林在火星演出  "基站"